# Haczar Criollo

Software Engineer

#### Personal Info

750 NE 199th St, North Miami Beach, FL 33179

(224) 600-0831

HaczarCriollo@gmail.com

@haczar\_criollo

HaczarCriollo.com

#### Skills

#### Game Engines:

- Unreal Engine 4
- Unity Engine

#### **Version Control:**

- Perforce
- TortoiseSVN
- Github

#### **VFX**

- Cascade/Niagara
- Houdini

#### **Graphics Editing**

- Adobe Photoshop
- Krita
- GIMP

#### 3D Modeling

- Blender
- Gravity Sketch

### Languages

#### Programming Languages

- C#
- C / C++
- Java

#### Spoken Languages

- English
- Spanish

Software Engineering Graduate with a passion and focus on immersive technologies (Virtual/Augmented/Mixed Reality). My goal is to provide clear and efficient solutions for real time simulations whether controlled or dynamic. Currently, I am a generalist having experience in all aspects in real time development from programming to VFX to animation. I am hoping to improve my craft in creating mechanics with all prior experience in mind.

### Experience

## Unity VR Developer | Florida International University | Fire360 Incident Command Simulator Nov 2017 - Dec 2020

- Worked on gameplay mechanics, modeling, texturing, animation, VFX, performance and optimizations.
- Provided technical support to both graduate and undergraduate university students with debugging and integration with various student VR projects.

## Unreal VR Developer | Florida International University | First Year Experience: Community VR Feb 2020 - Nov 2020

- Developed a multiplayer experience application for students with the objective of applying "Communication, Collaboration, Creativity, and Critical Thinking" using Unreal Engine 4.24.
- Managed team and applied efficient workflow throughout the programming, UI, environment design process to deliver quick sprint turnovers.

#### Unity Developer | Florida International University | Virtual Forest Sept 2020 - Nov 2020

- Optimized existing project to run on wider range of pc/mac hardware.
- Provided distribution method (PC/MacOS installers) with documentation.

#### Unreal VR Developer | Realities Future LLC | Co-Location Prototype Sept 2019 – Mar 2020

- R&D a polished prototype intended for demoing with a team of 3 developers.
- Tested the extensibility of tracking hardware native to Oculus Quest while developing a prototype application using Unreal Engine, the VR Expansion Plugin, and Antilatency hardware.

## Unreal VR Developer | Helm Systems | Soulkeeper VR Sept 2019 – Mar 2020

- · AI Programming, Gameplay programming, Gameplay implementation and performance optimization.
- Demonstrator at trade shows and public showcases/events.

#### Education

Florida International University | Bachelor's Degree | Computer Science: Software Engineering Track Spring 2017 – Fall 2020 GPA: 3.12